well very good so good morning everybody
很好，很好，大家早上好
how are you I don't expect a response I
你好吗，我不希望得到回应
just I just hope you register that I
我只是希望你注册我
care I'm excited to be here I hope you
关心我很高兴能在这里我希望你
are as well
也是
right so we're gonna go through a lot of
对，所以我们要经历很多
stuff today we're gonna cover a lot of
今天的事情，我们将涵盖很多
stuff in the world of reactive spring so
反应性弹簧的世界里的东西
I always like to start my talks with the
我总是喜欢与
little preface that that we're going to
我们要去的小序言
go through a lot of things the whole
经历了很多事情
point of this talk isn't in one hour to
这次演讲的重点不在一个小时内
sort of mint you as masters of all all
像所有大师一样造币厂
things reactive in spring but it's more
春季有反应，但更多
to sort of register what is possible and
排序注册什么是可能的，以及
to see what's possible and I know that
看看有什么可能，我知道
since you are all very intrepid and
因为你们都很勇敢
entrepreneurial you'll be able to go out
有创业精神的你就可以出去
there and find the details and I want to
在那里找到细节，我想
give you this github repository as a
给你这个github存储库作为一个
sort of a first step so that's out there
第一步，所以就在那里
on github get up calm long flux quick
在github上起床冷静长通量快速
service and then there of course guides
服务，然后有课程指南
it spring i/o for such guides where
它会为此类指南提供I / O
you'll find all manner of different
您会发现各种不同的方式
introductions to all things spring and
春天和万物的介绍
and reactive and of course if you have
和反应性，当然如果你有
questions don't ever hesitate to reach
问题永不犹豫
out to me I'm happy to answer questions
我很高兴回答问题
I'm on Twitter you can see that my
我在Twitter上可以看到我的
coordinates down there at Starbucks man
在星巴克男人那里协调
I'm happy to engage please find me there
我很高兴参与，请在那里找到我
and we can we can chat and of course you
我们可以聊天，当然您也可以
have email don't hesitate to find me
有电子邮件不要犹豫，找到我
there as well so either way works I am
还有，所以无论哪种方式我
at your service
乐意效劳
I am Josh long as was just well
我很久很久
explained
解释
I'm a spring developer advocate on the
我是春季开发者的倡导者
spring team I'm an open tours engineer a
春季团队，我是一个开放的巡回工程师
java champion and an author and trainer
Java冠军，作家和培训师
of numerous different videos and books
众多不同的视频和书籍
and then just finished recently my
然后最近刚完成我的
seventh video one of which is a building
第七个视频，其中一个是建筑物
micro services with spring Moot live
Spring Moot Live提供微服务
lessons these are on the Safari online
这些课程在Safari在线上
technical marketplace and of course I
技术市场，当然我
just finished my fifth book and this
刚读完我的第五本书，这个
book is called cloud native Java it's
这本书叫做云原生Java
all about how to build applications that
关于如何构建应用程序的所有内容
survive and thrive in the cloud and the
在云中生存并壮成长
the book is an O'Reilly book so if you
这本书是奥赖利的书，所以如果你
if you've ever read in a Riley book then
如果您曾经读过莱利书，
you know that the most important part of
你知道最重要的部分
the book is not really what's in between
这本书不是真的介于两者之间
the covers it's more the animal that is
掩盖的更多是动物
on the cover right that that animal
在那个动物的封面上
makes all the difference in the world
改变世界
for what you know people look to what
因为你知道人们看什么
they what they expect to find inside the
他们期望在里面找到什么
book so this animal was a hard sought
本书，所以这种动物是一个很难的
hard fought or chosen bird but we we
艰苦奋斗或选择的鸟，但我们
found it after a long many years look
经过多年的寻找才发现
for it right this bird is a a blue eared
为此，这只鸟是蓝耳的
Kingfisher it's a bird that is that is
翠鸟就是那只鸟
indigenous or of course as we'd say in
土著的，或者我们当然会说的
English native to the Indonesian Java
印尼爪哇语的英语母语
Island it's a bird it's indigenous to
岛上是只鸟，它是土生土长的鸟
Java or native to Java and birds they
Java或Java和鸟本身的本机
fly
飞
fly often through the clouds so this is
经常飞过云层，所以这是
a bird that is native to Java that flies
Java特有的飞鸟
through the clouds it's a cloud native
穿过云层，这是云原生
java bird it's a bird and never mind
Java鸟，这是鸟，没关系
anyway you'll get it it'll come there's
无论如何，你会得到它的到来
that and it's a blue eared Kingfisher
那是蓝耳翠鸟
right so that's a cool cool bird and of
对，那是一只很酷的鸟，
course I worked at pivotal and a pivotal
当然，我在关键和关键工作
we have a lot of good open-source
我们有很多很好的开源
software we care very much about open
我们非常关心开放的软件
source let's be very clear about that
消息来源让我们非常清楚
but it is not the thing that drives
但这不是驱动因素
people like me to spring out of bed what
像我这样的人从床上蹦出来
we care about more than anything is to
我们最关心的是
help organizations customers community
帮助组织客户社区
members it's a truck build better
成员，这是一辆卡车制造更好
software faster and safer and as part of
软件更快，更安全，并且作为
that we talk to organizations about how
我们与组织讨论如何
to increase their agility and as sort of
增加他们的敏捷性
a side effect of that progression that
这种进展的副作用是
moving that optimization for
将该优化移至
organizational agility is this move to
组织敏捷性是此举
micro services right micro services
微服务权微服务
allow organizations to decompose a large
允许组织分解大量
monolithic applications into smaller
整体应用变成更小的
batches of work a small batch of work
一小批工作
upon which a small team can iterate and
一个小团队可以在其上迭代并
then deploy into production and this has
然后部署到生产中
tangible benefits you see the act of
您看到的实际好处
decomposing your software into small
将您的软件分解成小块
singly focused internally consistent
专注于内部一致
reusable independently deployable
可重用，可独立部署
batches of work allows small teams it
分批工作允许小团队
enables small teams that is to say you
使小团队说你
don't need large teams working on one
不需要大团队一起工作
large monolithic code base you can have
您可以拥有的大型整体代码库
lots of small teams each focused on one
很多小团队都专注于一个
deliverable and that small team by
交付和那个小团队
virtue of the fact that it's staying
由于它一直存在
within its own component boundary has
在其自己的组件边界内具有
the ability to go faster right as long
能够一直走得更快的能力
as the surface area component boundary
作为表面积成分边界
of the component remains stable then the
的分量保持稳定，则
rest of the organization only needs to
组织的其余部分只需要
know about the API they don't have to
了解他们不需要的API
have long and tedious communication sort
沟通时间长而乏味
of interaction kind of conversations
互动式的对话
email threads that kind of thing that
电子邮件线程那种东西
gate our ability to go faster we can all
控制我们更快走的能力
sort of stay in our own proverbial swim
留在我们自己众所周知的游泳中
lane I think that allows for agility the
我认为这可以让敏捷
problem that a lot of people face when
很多人面对的问题
they move to this architecture of course
他们当然会迁移到这种架构
for all of its benefits and ability to
拥有所有的好处和能力
help organizations go faster is that of
帮助组织走得更快是
course when you move to this approach
当然，当您转向这种方法时
you're now introducing you know the
您正在介绍您知道
complexity of building a distributed
构建分布式系统的复杂性
system lots of small services talking to
系统中的许多小型服务与之交谈
each other over the network and of
通过网络和
course there are
当然有
patterns that you need to know about and
您需要了解的模式和
that address we will reliability there's
该地址，我们将可靠性
things you need to care about in terms
您需要注意的事情
of the ability to scale out there's a
向外扩展的能力
also two things that you need to care
还有两件事你需要注意
about that weren't necessarily problems
关于那不一定是问题
in the world of the monolith one thing
在巨石世界里一件事
that we we see a lot of people
我们看到很多人
struggling with is how to get the most
挣扎的是如何获得最大收益
efficiency out of their individual
个人效率
services right what we want to do is to
服务对，我们要做的就是
be able to move a lot of data across the
能够在整个
wire as efficiently as possible and when
尽可能高效地接线
I do it as reliably as possible and this
我尽可能可靠地做到这一点
is a you know this is a two-pronged
是一个你知道这是两个方面的
problem the the the hardest part I think
问题是我认为最难的部分
is the is getting the efficiency right
是正确的效率
the efficiency is something that we can
效率是我们可以做到的
we can take for granted at some point
我们可以在某个时候理所当然
because we can scale out but at some
因为我们可以扩大规模，但在某些方面
point we need to become more efficient
要提高效率
in the way we handle individual
以我们处理个人的方式
interactions especially as we start to
互动，尤其是当我们开始
move more and more data per request and
每个请求移动越来越多的数据，
this this requirement to send a lot of
这个要求寄了很多
data a potentially unlimited amount of
数据可能无限量
data across the wire becomes more and
线上的数据变得更多，
more pronounced as we scale up so what
当我们扩大规模时会更加明显
we're faced with is a very fundamental
我们面临的是非常根本的
question how do I move large amount of
问题我如何移动大量
data from one node to another how do i
从一个节点到另一个节点的数据
how do i facilitate that mostly i/o
我如何为大多数人提供便利
bound interaction between services and
服务与
this isn't a particularly new problem
这不是一个特别新的问题
right we've we've had in the java we've
对，我们已经在Java中拥有了
had an in the computer industry and the
在计算机行业有一个
computer scientists who've we've had a
我们有过的计算机科学家
lot of different support a lot of
很多不同的支持很多
different options here for for managing
此处用于管理的不同选项
this kind of complexity and in the in
这种复杂性
the java world of course we've we've had
我们拥有的Java世界
since day one the jdk inputstream and
从第一天开始，jdk inputstream和
outputstream abstraction now these input
现在这些输入的输出流抽象
stream and output stream abstractions
流和输出流抽象
have served as well but they are a very
曾经担任过，但他们是一个非常
very simplified abstraction they they
他们非常简化的抽象
hide some of the intrinsic power and
隐藏一些内在力量
complexity fair enough but they also
足够复杂，但他们也
hires them the power of the underlying
雇用他们底层的力量
sort of input an output stream output
输入种类输出流输出
model in the operating systems in most
大多数操作系统中的模型
operating systems right Network IO and
操作系统的网络IO和
most operating systems is asynchronous
大多数操作系统是异步的
right whereas the inputstream and
对，而输入流和
outputstream present a synchronous
输出流呈现同步
facade so fast forward to jdk 1.4 and
门面如此快速地前进到jdk 1.4和
you get some Java
你得到一些Java
yo you get channels you get found you
哟，你有渠道，你找到了你
know the ability to talk about
知道谈论的能力
asynchronous data that will eventually
最终将异步数据
arrive and this gives us they believe to
到达，这给了我们他们相信
start thinking about this you know to
开始考虑这个，你知道
start saying I have data that's that's
开始说我有那个数据
coming in on a socket and I need to be
进入插座，我需要
able to respond or when and only when
能够回应
that data is available and so this with
该数据可用，所以这与
channels you have the ability to say I
你有能力说我的频道
gave me a notification and in the
给了我一个通知，并在
meantime you're no longer blocked right
同时，您不再被封锁了
that that that whatever thread whatever
那那个无论什么线程
processing good even if it's just the
即使只是
main thread I can can do whatever else
我可以做的其他任何事情
that needs to do while it's waiting for
等待时需要做的
that channel to give it a notification
该频道向其发送通知
and so this is this is what we want this
这就是我们想要的
kind of functionality is what we want is
我们想要的是一种功能
the ability to talk about the fact that
谈论事实的能力
data is incoming but we have other
数据传入，但我们还有其他
things to do right it gives us the
做对的事情给了我们
ability to to unblock our interactions
解除阻碍我们互动的能力
and thus to be more efficient we can do
从而提高效率，我们可以做
more with the same resources that said
使用与上述相同的资源
this is a very low-level programming
这是一个很底层的程序
model right we didn't and we still don't
模范我们没有，我们仍然不
right most of our business logic in our
在我们的大多数业务逻辑中
functionality in terms of input streams
输入流方面的功能
and output streams so why would we any
和输出流，为什么我们要
sooner move to JDK and i/o and and news
更快地迁移到JDK，I / O和新闻
channels and so on right so this is a
渠道等等，所以这是一个
it's not quite suitable so what we've
这不太合适，所以我们已经
looked for it for the last 10 years you
在过去的十年里一直在寻找
know is some ways some paradigm to model
知道一些范式建模的方法
this kind of interaction this idea that
这种互动的想法
we have work that will arrive that will
我们有将要完成的工作
happen it'll happen asynchronously in
发生，它将异步发生
the future at some point in the future
未来的某个时刻
we don't know when and it could imply a
我们不知道何时，这可能意味着
lot of data or a little bit of data but
大量数据或少量数据，但是
the point is we can't be constrained and
关键是我们不能被束缚，
the program shouldn't have to change
该程序不必更改
depending on you know the size of the of
根据您知道的大小
the data so we've looked for some sort
数据，所以我们寻找了某种
of paradigm to address this and I think
范式来解决这个问题，我认为
you've seen a lot of really innovative
你已经看到了很多真正的创新
work in this space right I think that a
在这个空间工作，我认为
900-pound gorilla and of course is the
900磅的大猩猩当然是
work done by Microsoft's research around
微软的研究工作完成了
the reactive extensions for dotnet that
dotnet的反应性扩展
of course then inspired the folks at at
当然，然后在
Netflix who built our Ixtapa and and you
打造我们的Ixtapa的Netflix和您
know very shortly thereafter you see a
不久之后您就会知道
sort of deluge of different options in
大量的不同选择
the ecosystem so you've got you've got
生态系统，因此您拥有了
the folks at add light Bend nei of
在添加光的弯曲本尼的人
course typesafe who built a naka and
当然typesafe谁建立了naka和
that's one one way to sort of address
这是一种解决地址的方法
this kind of this kind of a
这种类型的
need and then you have a companies like
需要，然后你有一个像
Red Hat which have a have a technology
有技术的红帽
called vertex and of course we at this
叫做顶点，当然我们在这个
on the spring team both at VMware and
在VMware和Spring团队中
now of course here today we have a
现在当然今天在这里
project called reactor and reactor is a
一个叫做反应堆的项目，反应堆是一个
framework for modeling this sort of
建模这种框架
missing piece right the the missing
失物招领失物招领
quarter of the quadrant of types of
象限类型的四分之一
values that you can get back so think
您可以取回的价值，所以请思考
about how you would model in the JDK
关于如何在JDK中建模
today a service that's returning a
今天的服务正在返回
single value a single value of type of
单值类型的单值
string let's say you'd say I have a
字符串，假设您会说我有一个
method and the return value is string
方法，返回值为字符串
and if you had a method that returned
如果您有返回的方法
multiple values of type string T right
字符串T向右的多个值
you'd say collection of strength right
你会说收集力量的权利
collection generic type string if you
集合通用类型字符串，如果您
have I'm sorry for interrupting you
对不起打扰你了吗
there's some question about the slides
关于幻灯片有一些问题
so now right now we see only press white
所以现在现在我们只看到白色
and it says pivotal um springing 500
它说枢纽um springing 500
right that would yes okay
对，那会没事的
I don't decide I have to get through
我不认为我必须通过
this okay I just want to confirm it that
好的，我只想确认一下
it's not raised then sorry for in
它没有提出，然后对不起
trouble no problem
麻烦没问题
so we are we then have this a we have
所以我们是我们然后有一个我们有
multiple values we have a a method that
多个值，我们有一个方法
returns multiple values we say that's a
返回多个值，我们说这是一个
collection of string we have a method
字符串的收集我们有一个方法
that returns a single berry that's a
返回一个单一的浆果
string if we want to return a everyone's
字符串，如果我们想返回每个人的
have a method that returned a a single
有一个返回一个单一的方法
value asynchronously we'd say you know
异步价值我们会说你知道
using a JDK 8 we'd say here's a
使用JDK 8，我们会说这是一个
completable future of string right so
字符串的可完成未来
this is a mechanism that allows us to
这是一种使我们能够
get a notification when the value is
当值是
available even though it's not right now
即使不是现在也可以使用
all right it's it's a not a future it's
好吧，这不是未来，而是
better than the future I don't have to
比未来更好，我不必
poll I don't have to constantly ask for
民意测验，我不必不断地要求
the value I can just be notified and you
可以通知我的价值，您
know when it's available and that gives
知道什么时候可用，这给了
us three out of four of the kind of
我们四分之三
things that we want to model what what
我们想要建模什么的东西
is missing in this paradigm is how do we
这种范式中缺少的是我们如何
model how do we describe how do we talk
模拟我们如何描述我们如何交谈
about it potentially unlimited amount of
关于它可能无限量的
data that may be may be available later
可能稍后可用的数据
on in the future
在未来
a synchronously right and this is what's
一个同步的权利，这是什么
been missing and I think a lot of us and
失踪了，我想我们很多人
these in these different sort of corners
这些在不同的角落
of the ecosystem have been looking for
的生态系统一直在寻找
ways to address that and here you can
解决这个问题的方法，在这里您可以
see that there's been a lot of different
看到有很多不同
idea
理念
and we all sort of converged upon the
我们都汇聚在
the ideas that we we put together in the
我们将其整合在一起的想法
reactor streams initiative so the
反应堆主动行动
reactive streams initiative is a sort of
反应流倡议是一种
de facto standard that describes this
描述这一点的事实标准
this is this missing piece in the
这是这件遗失的东西
reactive streams initiative you have
你有反应性的主动行动
it's basically a specification a very
这基本上是一个规范
very tiny specification we describe four
非常小的规格，我们描述了四个
types for interfaces the first and most
接口的类型，第一个和大多数
important I think is the publisher a
我认为重要的是发布商
publisher is a if an object that
发布者是如果
produces values to which a subscriber
产生订户所依赖的价值
that's another interface may subscribe
那是另一个界面可能会订阅
and in so doing a subscription is
因此，订阅是
created so you have three interfaces
已创建，因此您具有三个界面
there so far a publisher a subscriber in
到目前为止，有一个发布者和一个订阅者
a subscription and if you have a
订阅，如果您有
component that produces values that is
产生值的组件
to say a publisher and that also then
说一个出版商，然后
subscribes to values from some other
从其他订阅
publisher then you have something called
发布者，那么你有一个叫做
a processor and a processor is our
一个处理器，一个处理器就是我们
fourth interface that's it
第四界面就是这样
that's the entirety of the reactive
这就是反应堆的全部
streams specification now this may seem
流规范，现在看来
enticing and you might be tempted to
诱人，您可能会想
rush out and to try and improve these
冲出去并尝试改善这些
interfaces and call yourselves reactive
界面，让自己反应
but I assure you this is a very bad idea
但我向你保证这是一个非常糟糕的主意
right there's a lot of convoluted work
正确的工作很多
that has to be done at the lower levels
必须在较低的级别上完成
to make this happen so we have
为了做到这一点，所以我们有
thankfully you know luckily we have an
幸运的是，您幸运地知道我们有一个
abundance of options here in the
这里有很多选择
ecosystem right the reactor streams
生态系统对反应堆流的影响
specification has been implemented by of
规范已由实施
course our own project reactor the akka
当然我们自己的项目反应堆akka
streams project my pin can use it as
流项目，我的图钉可以将其用作
well vertex influenced it as well and of
良好的顶点也影响了它
course rx Java - Dino so we have now
课程RX Java-Dino，所以我们现在有了
here a mechanism for interoperability
这里是互操作性的机制
and of course that work then inspired
当然，然后工作启发了
the sort of JDK 9 flow module right so
像这样的JDK 9流模块
that's another channel by which we can
这是我们可以通过的另一个渠道
see this this missing piece being
看到这件遗失的东西
addressed now reactive streams it gives
现在解决了它提供的反应流
us a very very low level understanding a
我们对知识的了解非常低
single type or a single set of types a
单一类型或单一类型集合
very small set of types along which we
我们遵循的类型非常少
can sort of agree mmm but it's I think
可以同意mmm，但是我认为
by itself not all that useful in the
本身并不是所有有用的
same way that arrays are valuable as a
数组作为
common transport mechanism as a common
共同的运输机制
way to carry data back and forth from
来回携带数据的方式
one component to another it's still very
一个组件到另一个组件仍然非常
low level we we tend
我们倾向于低水平
do more interesting things with our data
用我们的数据做更多有趣的事情
than just store it right we need to be
不仅仅是存储正确，我们需要
able to process it to transform it to
能够对其进行处理以将其转换为
filter it etcetera etc so we we look for
过滤等，所以我们寻找
higher order operators dia sells things
高阶经营者dia出售东西
like that that comes service there and
这样的服务在那里
here reactor comes into its own right we
在这里，反应堆变成了自己的权利
have a very rich set of API is a very
有非常丰富的API集
rich set of capabilities and reactor
丰富的功能和反应堆
project now is that enough I'd still say
现在的项目就足够了，我仍然会说
no reactor in of itself while very
本身没有反应器
interesting is focused on being a
有趣的是专注于成为
reactive runtime it doesn't necessarily
反应性运行时，不一定
address the concerns of you know higher
解决您所关心的问题
order functionality like building web
订购功能，例如建立网站
services and data access and security
服务以及数据访问和安全性
and so on and here is where our story
等等，这就是我们的故事
begins
开始
you see we just last week released
你看我们上周才发布
spring files and spring 5 has a number
spring文件和spring 5有一个数字
of great features including a canine
特色，包括犬
support while having a jk8 baseline I
在拥有jk8基线时提供支持
didn't include support for Java EE 7 and
不包括对Java EE 7和
Java 8 it's you know filled with great
Java 8充满了强大的功能
features but my favorite feature is the
功能，但我最喜欢的功能是
support for building reactive
支持建立反应式
applications and that starts at the web
应用程序，并且从网络开始
layer in Spring Framework 5 where we've
Spring Framework 5中的层
introduced a new new runtime so I'm
引入了一个新的新运行时，所以我
going to talk about all that stuff today
今天要谈论所有这些东西
now going back to this idea going back
现在回到这个想法
to the project reactor it's important to
对于项目反应堆，重要的是
understand that reactor bases it's two
了解反应堆的基础是两个
main types on the reactive streams
反应流的主要类型
publisher type so we have two types in
发布者类型，因此我们有两种类型
reactor one is called a mono a mono is a
反应堆称为单声道单声道为
publisher that is bounded it's either 0
受限制的发布者为0
or 1 value right so you have no value or
或1个正确的值，所以您没有任何价值或
you have 1 by odes it's still publisher
您有1 by odes，它仍然是发布者
it's just a publisher that can only ever
只是一个发行商
produce one or the other now of course
当然现在可以生产一个或另一个
you can still handle it in terms of the
您仍然可以按照
publisher contract in which case all
发行人合同，在所有情况下
your consuming code would be none the
您的消费代码将不是
wiser
明智的
it's just that they would only get one
只是他们只会得到一个
value another type that we have is
重视我们拥有的另一种类型是
called a flux FL UX it's a publisher
被称为flux FL UX，它是发布者
that produces 0 to n values and the
产生0到n的值，并且
reason that these are these you know
你知道这些的原因
distinguishing types are useful is
区分类型是有用的
mostly for documentation it's mostly for
主要用于文档，主要用于
giving giving a cue to the consumer
给消费者一个提示
about what the intent is imagine you're
关于意图是什么，想像你是
trying to render a a screen and the
试图渲染一个屏幕和
screen has a text box that's probably
屏幕上有一个可能是
amano right versus a grid in this case
天野右与网格在这种情况下
you can expect to use a flux right
你可以期望使用助焊剂吧
otherwise you wouldn't have any idea
否则你不会有任何想法
about what to set up what what's a look
关于如何设置外观
for here now this gives us fertile
因为现在这给了我们沃土
ground for for some you know interesting
为一些你知道的有趣的事情打下基础
apps and well we could build an any
应用，我们可以构建任何
number of conceivable apps out there I
我可以想到的应用数量
want to keep our domain as simple and
希望保持我们的域名简单易用
trivial as possible so I like to I I was
琐碎的，所以我喜欢
thinking with I was thinking about this
想着我在想这个
with my with my friend mark heckler the
与我和我的朋友马克·赫克特
other day we were thinking about having
前几天我们在考虑
some sort of sample app some sort of app
某种示例应用程序某种类型的应用程序
that we could use on the Internet right
我们可以在互联网上使用的权利
what if we had some sort of app that
如果我们有某种应用程序
allowed us to talk about and interact
允许我们谈论和互动
with movies for example now in English
例如现在有英文电影
it's a colloquialism to say that when
口语化是说
you have one movie it's a movie if you
你有一部电影，如果你有一部电影
have a if you wanna use slang you can
如果您想使用语，可以
say it's a flick if you have multiple
说如果你有多个，那是轻弹
movies we call that we call that we call
我们所谓的电影我们称之为的电影
those flicks right and so we're thinking
那些轻弹，所以我们在考虑
what if we had some sort of service and
如果我们提供某种服务怎么办？
again hear me out this might be a little
再次听到我的声音可能有点
crazy but what if we had some sort of
疯了，但是如果我们有某种
service where we could work with flicks
我们可以轻弹的服务
and interact with flicks over the net
并通过网络与电影互动
and again I know this is preposterous so
再一次，我知道这很荒谬
but again just hear me out we want to
但还是要听我说我们想
have some sort of service to work with
有某种服务可以使用
with flicks over the net and I was
在网上轻弹，我当时
thinking we were thinking we could call
以为我们以为可以打电话
it Netflix
它是Netflix
what do you think because of reactor and
您对反应堆的看法如何？
flex and no okay well anyway we're gonna
弹性和不好，反正我们要
go with that and we need to build a new
这样做，我们需要建立一个新的
service and of course I'm gonna use my
服务，当然我要用我的
favorite tool to do the job I'll use
最喜欢的工具来完成我将要使用的工作
IntelliJ right so I've got IntelliJ here
IntelliJ对，所以我这里有IntelliJ
now normally at this point I take us to
现在通常在这一点上，我带我们去
start that spring that IO and that's a
从那个春天开始IO，那是一个
great place to start but it is if you're
一个很好的起点，但是如果你
using IntelliJ which I expect a lot of
我期望使用IntelliJ
the people in this audience are then
然后，这些观众中的人
there's a very handy little option here
这里有一个非常方便的小选择
create new project and create new
创建新项目并创建新
project opens up a wizard and when you
项目会打开一个向导，当您
go to the wizard you are given a chance
进入向导，您将有机会
to point at a particular start the
指向一个特定的开始
spring Guerrero permutation and there we
春天的格雷罗排列，我们在那里
can specify the name of artifact so flux
可以指定工件的名称，以便助焊剂
flicks service and we're gonna make this
轻弹服务，我们将做这个
a complan project just because it's
一个complan项目，只是因为
fairly straightforward if you know Java
如果您了解Java，则非常简单
and I figure this is a good chance to
我认为这是一个很好的机会
demonstrate it and then we're gonna hit
演示它，然后我们将击中
next and that'll show us all the options
接下来，这将向我们展示所有选项
now here I'm gonna choose spring boot to
现在在这里，我要选择 spring boot
auto snapshots
自动快照
isten graders in the spring boot to that
春季靴中的isten平地机
spring boot is a fully integrated
弹簧靴是完全集成的
reactive sort of framework it's gonna be
反应性的框架
released in December of this year we
我们在今年12月发布
expect and then it'll you know all the
期待，然后你会知道所有
other stuff that we all the other stuff
其他的东西，我们所有其他的东西
that we've done in the ecosystem bubbles
我们在生态系统泡沫中所做的
up into this release so Spring Framework
直到这个版本，所以Spring框架
5 which of course was released last week
5当然是上周发布的
spring security 5 spring data K spring
弹簧安全5弹簧数据K弹簧
spring and QP all the other things that
Spring和QP所有其他的事情
have reactive support that will bubble
有反应性的支持会冒泡
up into spring boot to it I don't so
到春天的靴子，我不是这样
we're gonna use here reactive web
我们将在这里使用反应性网络
support will use reactive MongoDB will
支持将使用反应式MongoDB将
use reactive security now we have here
现在使用反应式安全
yeah you know I saw a chose reactive
是的，你知道我看到了一种选择的反应
MongoDB let's take a look at those
MongoDB让我们来看看那些
options again here we have reactive not
再次选择这里我们有反应性不
going to be reactive Cassandra reactive
将是反应性的Cassandra反应性
web and reactive all Redis now there are
网络和反应式所有Redis现在都有
a number of different good number of
一些不同的好数目
different and very good options here and
不同的和非常好的选择，在这里和
but so far these are a subset by
但到目前为止，这些是
definition they're a subset of the
定义它们是
supported options first in spring data
春季数据优先支持的选项
so spring that of course is the umbrella
所以春天当然是雨伞
projects that we used to address no
我们曾经解决过的项目
sequel sort of interactions and data
交互和数据的续集
processing functionality and because
处理功能，以及
even in spring data we have one more
即使在春季数据中，我们还有一个
option that we don't have here surfaced
我们在这里没有的选择浮出水面
in our spring boot auto configuration
在我们的春季启动自动配置中
and that is reactive Couchbase right so
那是反应性的Couchbase对，所以
that's that's not here yet but it will
那还没到这里，但是会
be and and then even that is a subset of
be and然后甚至是那的子集
course of course of what spring data
当然有哪些春季数据
itself support you may you may know that
本身支持您，您可能知道
spring data supports any number of
spring数据支持任意数量的
different other technologies including
其他不同的技术，包括
most notably kpa now JPA is a a ORM
最明显的是kpa，现在JPA是a ORM
framework it's a norm technology it's a
框架这是一种规范技术，这是一种
standard it is often based on things
它通常是基于事物的
like the Kochs link and and hibernate
像Kochs链接，然后休眠
well we don't have at the lowest levels
好吧，我们没有最低的水平
of JPA the ability to do reactive
JPA的反应能力
programming right JBC is a blocking api
正确的编程JBC是一个阻止api
now we could create a reactive facade on
现在我们可以在
top of this fundamentally blocking thing
根本阻止的事情的顶部
but we think we're of the mind that
但我们认为我们的想法是
that's sort of fundamentally not very
从根本上说不是很
useful it would be just as important for
有用的对于
in performance as a as I'm blocking API
就像我阻塞API一样
while being you know
当你知道的时候
we'd have to change things just to get
我们必须改变一些东西才能得到
nothing to get no benefits to it so
什么也没有得到任何好处，所以
we're not gonna try and do that we're
我们不会尝试去做到这一点
not gonna turn those things around now
现在不打算扭转这些事情
we're inspired I think we're all hopeful
我们受到鼓舞，我认为我们都充满希望
about the recently released recent
关于最近发布的
recent really announced JB's reactive
最近真正宣布的JB反应式
JDBC work being done by Oracle you know
您知道Oracle正在完成JDBC工作
the bit the details of which they begin
他们开始的细节
to announce just in the last few days in
在最近几天宣布
Java one so that's interesting we'll see
Java之一，这很有趣，我们将看到
where that goes but for now we're going
哪里去了，但现在我们要去
to use the technologies that are
使用的技术是
properly and fully reactive so we're
适当而充分地反应，所以我们
gonna stick with reactive MongoDB now
现在会坚持使用反应性MongoDB
again a number of different choices here
再次有许多不同的选择
but reactive MongoDB works just fine so
但是反应性MongoDB可以正常工作，所以
we'll hit next and we'll get ourselves a
我们接下来要打，我们自己
new project hit go
新项目开始
all right so we have a new service and
好的，所以我们有一项新服务，
the first thing I want to do is I wanna
我想做的第一件事就是我想
I want to disable the security here
我想在这里禁用安全性
because that's not gonna do anything for
因为那不会做任何事情
us just yet so let's go back to our
我们还没有，所以让我们回到我们的
build and we'll build a a new service so
构建，我们将构建一个新服务，因此
here we are spring boots starters
这是我们的 spring boot 首发
security reactive everything else is as
安全反应其他一切都一样
we expected you'll notice that the
我们希望您会注意到
spring spring air sizer automatically
弹簧弹簧自动空气尺
supports Cottman so we have Conklin
支持科特曼，所以我们有康克林
support there we have the cotton SD it's
支持那里，我们有棉花SD
you know a standard library we have the
您知道我们有一个标准库
runtime it's etc we have a common
运行时等我们有一个共同点
compiler plugin all plugged in and
编译器插件全部插入并且
everything I mean everything has just
我所有的一切都只是
been set up free so we don't have to
已免费设置，因此我们不必
worry about anything else now we can go
担心别的事情，现在我们可以去了
to the code and start building an
代码，然后开始构建
application so the first thing that
应用程序，所以第一件事
we're gonna do here is we're gonna build
我们要在这里做我们要建立
a date a model right we're gonna build a
约会的权利，我们将建立一个
model to talk about movies now this is a
模特谈论电影，现在这是一个
regular spring good application so if
定期春季良好的应用程序，如果
you haven't seen Kotlin before this is
你还没看过Kotlin
basically the public static void main
基本上公共静态无效主体
entry point into the application in
进入应用程序的入口
Kotlin the name of their girls on the
Kotlin上女孩的名字
left and the types on the right so it's
左边和右边的类型，所以
args colon or a string but otherwise
args冒号或字符串，否则
this should look I think altogether very
我认为这应该看起来非常
familiar if you've ever used spring
如果您曾经使用过弹簧，请熟悉
boots so let's see we're gonna build the
靴子，让我们看看我们要打造
a type to model a movie now this is
现在是电影建模的一种类型
gonna be a movie that has a couple of
将会是一部有几部电影的电影
fields I could say I could just do this
我可以说我可以做到这一点
I could say bar ID equals string so the
我可以说酒吧ID等于字符串，所以
type of string and I want the type to be
字符串的类型，我希望该类型为
knowable so I want I want to be like
博学，所以我想成为
that and I wanted to have an a default
那我想要一个默认值
value of null right so VAR in this case
空值的正确值，因此在这种情况下为VAR
tells Kotlin that it's a mutable very
告诉科特林，这很容易变
variable and say I can change it so I
变量并说我可以更改它，所以我
could do that and I could quit you know
可以做到，我可以辞职
getters and setters if I wanted to but
吸气剂和二传手如果我想但是
this is a lot of work what I really want
这是我真正想要的很多工作
to do is I just want to let Kotlin do
我只想让科特林做
that work cuz I'm trying to do this to
该工作，因为我试图做到这一点
get a job at being basically so instead
从根本上得到一份工作
I'll save our ID string question mark
我将保存我们的ID字符串问号
equals null
等于null
okay and I'll save our title string
好的，我将保存标题字符串
question mark equals no no this is my
问号等于否否这是我的
basic javabean I want to make it a
基本的javabean，我想做一个
document so I'll use the spring data
文档，所以我将使用spring数据
document annotation here and I'll say
文档注释在这里，我会说
add ID there we are so that's my my
在这里添加ID，这就是我的
entity right that's gonna be a spring
实体权利将成为春天
data among going to be document that
数据将成为文档
I'll have a primary key kind of thing a
我将拥有主键之类的东西
key called ID and the default values are
名为ID的键，默认值为
are no and they are knowable
不是，他们是众所周知的
it'll have getters it'll have setters I
它会有吸气剂我会有吸气剂
have all that now I want to make this a
现在所有的东西我都想做
data class for I totally go one step
数据类我完全走了一步
further to give me a equal and I schools
进一步给我平等，我上学
and so on things like that I can use to
诸如此类，我可以用来
support equality right alright so now
支持平等权利好吧，现在
I've got a movie and what I want to do I
我有电影，我想做什么
want to be able to persist or interact
希望能够坚持或互动
with instances of this entity with the
与该实体的实例
underlying data tier in this case
在这种情况下，基础数据层
MongoDB so I need to write a repository
MongoDB，所以我需要写一个仓库
repositories a design pattern designed
仓库设计的设计模式
to support you know dated the data
支持您知道过时的数据
minimal data management lifecycle so
最小化数据管理生命周期，因此
I'll say movie repository okay
我会说电影资料库还可以
and we're going to extend the reactive
我们将扩大反应性
Mongo repository now the reactive manga
Mongo仓库现在是反应漫画
repository just like any other
仓库与其他仓库一样
repository expects two types they
存储库期望两种类型
expects the type that we want to
期望我们想要的类型
interact with this is in a movie and the
与此互动是在电影中，
type of the primary key now that's it I
现在是主键的类型
don't have to I don't even have to do
不必我什至不必做
that right this is enough to get what I
没错，这足以让我得到
want now this reactive manga repository
现在要这个反应性漫画库
is the same as any other repository
与任何其他存储库相同
you've probably seen in spring data
您可能已经在春季数据中看到了
except that the return types are these
除了返回类型是这些
publisher subtypes or monos and fluxes
发布者子类型或单声道和流量
and so on and further they accept
等等，他们进一步接受
publishers right so we can accept a
出版商权利，所以我们可以接受
publisher and return a specific type of
发布商并返回特定类型的
publisher so we'd get all that for free
发布商，所以我们将免费获得所有这些
and now we can save some sample data in
现在我们可以在其中保存一些示例数据
the database now I'm gonna have a bean
现在我要数据库
here the bean of type you know Runner
这是您知道类型的豆
and this is going to be an application
这将是一个应用程序
runner so I'm gonna create a lambda
跑步者，所以我要创建一个lambda
again this is a great callback interface
再次，这是一个很棒的回调接口
that spring boot provides and the
弹簧靴提供的
callback interface has one method void
回调接口有一种方法无效
run now of course in Kotlin we can
现在当然可以在Kotlin运行
create a lambda then address of that
创建一个lambda，然后输入该地址
like this now the void run method
现在像这样空运行方法
has arguments here right we can we can
这里有论点，我们可以，我们可以
choose to since we have just one
选择，因为我们只有一个
argument we couldn't choose to create a
我们无法选择创建一个参数
parameter like that or we can just leave
这样的参数，否则我们可以离开
alone we don't have to don't specified
一个人，我们不必指定
it'll be available through the implicit
它可以通过隐式使用
parameter here called it alright so
这里的参数还好吧
there's the being variable and since
存在变量，因为
we're not even gonna use it this case it
我们甚至都不会在这种情况下使用它
really doesn't make any sense to take
真的没有任何意义
care about it so let's now write some
关心它，所以让我们现在写一些
sample data to the database so movies
将数据采样到数据库，以便电影
equals when we create a flux here just
等于当我们在这里创建通量时
of some sample data and I like to use
一些示例数据，我喜欢使用
data that's that's on the theme of
以主题为基础的数据
reactive programming and the theme of
反应式编程和主题
you know functional reactive programming
你知道函数式反应式编程
so I'm gonna create some movie titles
所以我要拍一些电影
here based on those themes so how about
根据这些主题在这里如何
this one this is from from our friend
这是我们朋友送来的
the one the only the amazing Phil Webb
唯一令人惊奇的菲尔·韦伯
the co-founder of Spring boo they'll be
Spring boo的共同创始人
Silence of the Lambs right that's a good
沉默的羔羊是不错的选择
one over we're gonna use that movie
一个，我们要用那部电影
there there's an anime with the word
有一个动漫这个词
flux in it so we can say Aeon Flux
不断变化，所以我们可以说Aeon Flux
there's a there's a movie where they
有一部电影，他们
talk about a flux capacitor
谈论磁通电容器
that's back to the future right so
回到未来吧
number of different options here if you
如果您在此处选择不同的数量
think of some others please don't
想到别人，请不要
hesitate to send them out on Twitter I'd
犹豫要在Twitter上将它们发送出去
love to hear them so here we are there's
很想听听他们的声音，所以我们在这里
a a publisher of three strings I'm going
一个我要出版的三弦琴
to turn those three strings into movies
把那三根弦变成电影
so I'm gonna say that I want to save the
所以我要说我想保存
data now of course I wanna save the data
现在的数据我当然想保存数据
using the movie repository here we are
在这里使用电影资料库
salt inject that as a collaborating
盐注入作为合作
object i'll say mr dot save movie title
我会说点先生保存电影标题的对象
equals it remember that's the implicit
等于它记得那是隐含的
parameter here for this lambda and since
此参数的参数，因为
it's a parameter and it's a lambda i
这是一个参数，它是一个lambda
don't have to actually encapsulate this
不必实际封装
method call with parenthesis though I
虽然我带括号的方法调用
could write it's just a syntax shortcut
可以写的只是语法快捷方式
here so they were done saving each
在这里，他们完成了保存每个
record now that gives me a publisher of
现在记录下来，这使我成为
movies rights and I can see that I can
电影版权，我可以看到
confirm as much as I want by assigning
通过分配来尽可能多地确认
this to a tight line it's optional in
这是一条紧线，它是可选的
this case it'll be type inference but
在这种情况下，它将是类型推断，但是
for our purposes it's just it's just a
就我们的目的而言，这只是一个
useful to know that now we're gonna save
知道现在我们要保存很有用
all this data but before we save over
所有这些数据，但在保存之前
there I want to delete all the existing
我要删除所有现有的
data so what I want to do is I want to
数据，所以我要做的就是
say delete all now I want to make sure
说我现在要删除所有
that this happens before everything else
在其他所有事情发生之前
so one way I could do that is to say
所以我可以做到的一种方法是说
block now this is a terrible idea
现在阻止，这是一个可怕的想法
I showed this code to my to my
我向我展示了此代码
significant other and she looked at me
重要的另一个，她看着我
like I was not very bright so don't do
就像我不是很聪明所以不要
this this is a terrible thing you've
这是一件可怕的事
you've got this wonderful reactive API
你有这个很棒的反应式API
and here we are
我们在这里
okay what we want to do is we want to
好的，我们要做的是
say delete everything then process this
说删除所有内容然后处理
publisher of movies right so we've got
电影发行商的权利，所以我们有
movies and then we want to let's see we
电影，然后我们想看看我们
want to say
想说
we want to say that we want to return
我们想说我们想回来
everything that comes back from the
从...回来的一切
database so when we turn everything
数据库，所以当我们打开一切
there we are
我们在那里
and then we want to subscribe and this
然后我们要订阅
last method is the most important what
最后一种方法最重要
we're doing is we're saying when you
我们正在做的是我们在说什么时候
have finished building up the graph the
完成了图的建立
of operations here right I'm building a
我正在建立一个
reactive pipeline if you well these
反应性管道，如果您能做到这些
first three operations are a pipeline
前三个操作是管道
I'm saying do this then this then then
我是说先做这个然后
this nothing happens until something
这什么都不会发生
subscribes to it or blocks it right so
订阅或阻止它，这样
and blocking ultimately just subscribe
并最终阻止只是订阅
so what I'm doing is I'm I'm kicking off
所以我在做的是我在开始
the pipeline I'm I'm executing the the
我正在执行的管道
definition here and I'm selling I'm
定义在这里，我在卖我
telling a the publisher that I'm
告诉发布者我
interested in getting the values that it
有兴趣获取它的价值
can emit so here we are we going to
可以发射，所以在这里我们要
print everything that comes back when on
打印打开时返回的所有内容
the consoles okay so now let's run the
控制台好了，现在让我们运行
application
应用
you
您
all right so there we are there's our
好吧，所以我们在那里
application with the three records on
具有三个记录的应用程序
the console and that would teams have
控制台，团队将拥有
worked so Goods now we can create a
如此有效，现在我们可以创建商品了
let's create a service right now what we
让我们现在创建一个服务
ultimately ultimately want to do is kind
最终最终想做的是善良的
of web app web endpoint but in order to
Web应用程序Web终结点，但为了
that let's build a service that services
让我们建立一项服务
our business logic so I want to create a
我们的业务逻辑，所以我想创建一个
movie service like so and the service
像这样的电影服务和服务
will in turn inject or work with the
反过来将注入或与
movie repository so I'm gonna say
电影资料库，所以我要说
private Val M our movie repository and
私人Val M我们的电影资料库和
the service is just going to serve a
该服务将服务于
surface higher-order business logic
表面高阶业务逻辑
right so we're gonna say that we have an
对，所以我们要说我们有一个
endpoint here that returns all the
这里的端点返回所有
records I'm gonna say m r dot find all
记录，我要说点先生找到所有
and we'll have another one that says
我们会再说一个
that we're gonna return a particular one
我们要返回一个特定的
by its ID so there's this mr dot find by
通过其ID，因此找到了这个先生点
ID ID and for this last endpoint what I
ID ID和最后一个端点我
wanted to I'm gonna have an endpoint
想要我有一个终点
that can be turn in the events let's say
可以在事件中说
I let's suppose I had the opportunity to
我想我有机会
somehow log into the service and tale
以某种方式登录服务和故事
all the logs reflecting all the output
反映所有输出的所有日志
from all the services that would be very
从所有的服务中
interesting I think by the way I I don't
有趣的是我想我不
mean to go pass is too quickly if I'm
如果我是
you know there's no there's no
你知道没有没有
statements and this language right so
陈述和正确的语言，所以
it's everything is an expression so here
这就是一切，所以在这里
I have a method that it's returning a
我有一个方法，它返回一个
single value there's no need to create a
单一值，无需创建
parenthesis parenthesis and all that
括号括号等
stuff I can just and and I can just say
我可以并且我可以说的东西
the result of this method when you call
调用时此方法的结果
it is this the statement here right and
这是这里的陈述
of course interactive world you can
当然，您可以互动的世界
change these methods very nicely so you
很好地更改这些方法，以便您
get one long statement or one sorry one
得到一份长声明或一项对不起的声明
long expression to get to turn back
长长的表情要回头
that's very convenient now this last
这最后很方便
endpoint here is going to be as I say a
终点在这里就像我说的那样
and endpoint a service that allows me to
并终结一项服务，使我能够
look at all of the the activity for a
查看所有活动
given movie let's say so I can see who's
给定电影，那么我可以看谁
streaming the videos I could stream the
流的视频，我可以流
information about people who are
有关人的信息
streaming all the videos now of course I
当然，现在流式传输所有视频
don't actually have yet a bazillion
实际上还没有八兆
users logged into the system
用户登录系统
looking at the output of the you know
看着你知道的输出
look at all the different movies and so
看所有不同的电影等等
we have no real sample data so let's
我们没有真正的样本数据，所以让我们
just think until we make it we're gonna
只是想想，直到我们做到这一点
stream all the streams we're gonna cross
流我们将要穿越的所有流
the streams to borrow from Ghostbusters
向捉鬼敢死队借来的小溪
right so I'm gonna say fun event and
对，所以我要说有趣的事件，
we're gonna look for all the events for
我们将寻找所有的活动
a particular movie and what we
一部特定的电影以及我们
what we're going to do is when I
我们要做的是当我
generate we're going to synthesize a new
产生，我们将合成一个新的
a new new record okay and the movie is
一个新的新记录好了，电影是
going to be the the record it's gonna be
将会成为唱片
of type movie event right so this is
电影事件类型正确的，所以这是
gonna be yet another data class it'll be
将会是另一个数据类
it'll contain two thing it'll contain
它会包含两件事
the movie ID string question mark equal
电影ID字符串问号等于
to null and it'll contain the date right
为null，它将包含正确的日期
now we could use the name when but this
现在我们可以使用名称，但是
is actually a reserved word so if he
实际上是保留字，如果他
went into this if you find a variable
如果找到一个变量就进入这个
name that is now a reserved word in
现在是保留字的名称
common it's a back tick right but for
常见的是向后打勾，但对于
our purposes let's just keep it as date
我们的目的就是让它保持最新
since we don't want to be in the
因为我们不想进入
situation where we're doing things that
我们正在做的事情
the compiler wants to do for us or to
编译器想要为我们做
otherwise so we're gonna call it the
否则，我们将其称为
movie ID and we're gonna give it the the
电影ID，我们要给它
taejun they're gonna both be notable and
太俊，他们都将是著名的
default to null okay so this is our a
默认为null好吧，这是我们的
wrapper type that will describe both
包装类型将描述两个
what movie is being washed and when it
洗什么电影以及何时洗
was being watched so we don't air it now
正在被观看，所以我们现在不播放
a series of data we're gonna use a man a
我们将要使用的一系列数据
call back here that expects a sink and
在这里回呼，期望会下沉，
the sink is asynchronous
接收器是异步的
Cronus sink of type movie event and in
电影事件和中的Cronus Sink
the sink we're going to generate a new
我们要生成新的接收器
value so I'm gonna say a dot next
值，所以我接下来要说一个点
creating a movie event I'm a past and of
创建电影活动我是过去的事
course the movie ID and a new date all
当然是电影ID和新日期
right now that's gonna generate that's
现在会产生的是
going to create a publisher that will
要创建一个发布商
have a continuous never-ending
持续不断
sequence of movie events as long as
电影事件的顺序只要
there's heat in the universe there will
宇宙中有热量
be movie events which isn't exactly what
电影事件，这不完全是
we want because I want to be able to I
我们想要，因为我希望能够
mean we're you know we're not gonna have
意思是我们你知道我们不会有
a trillion users watching movies every
每万亿用户观看电影
every microsecond right we're gonna have
我们将拥有的每一微秒
a stream of data and let's say that we
数据流，假设我们
have a monitor make loaded service and
有一个监视器使加载的服务和
so we get a get a new stream every
所以我们得到了一个新的流
second since I don't actually have all
第二，因为我实际上没有全部
those users logged into the system let's
这些用户登录系统后，
take advantage in the fact that behind
利用以下事实
the scenes behind this wonderful
这个奇妙的幕后花絮
reactive reactor API we have a scheduler
反应堆API我们有一个调度程序
right so we're gonna actually tell the
对，所以我们实际上要告诉
scheduler to delay the elements that are
调度程序延迟元素
coming out of this publisher by a
由该出版商发行
certain amount of seconds all right so
一定的秒数，好吧
those are our delayed publisher and I
那些是我们的延迟出版商，我
think that's it I think that'll give us
认为就是这样，我认为这会给我们
our our very simple service and we can
我们非常简单的服务，我们可以
use that to build an arrest in point so
用它来建立逮捕点
so go down here we can say want to build
所以去这里我们可以说想建立
a spring MVC style rest controller now
一个春季MVC风格的休息控制器
this is going to be very submit very
这将是非常提交非常
similar and very familiar to anybody
相似且非常熟悉的人
who's used spring MVC before but this is
谁曾经使用过Spring MVC，但这是
let's be very clear not spring MVC this
让我们非常清楚不是Spring MVC这个
is actually a new a net new runtime
实际上是一个新的
called spring web flex spring web flux
称为弹簧腹板挠性弹簧腹板通量
is a a brand new web runtime it has
是一个全新的Web运行时
similar support it has annotations that
类似的支持，它具有注释
are similar to spring MVC except that
与Spring MVC相似，除了
it's fully geared from the ground up to
从头到脚都充分装备
be reactive is to support reactive
反应是支持反应
processing and so some things are gonna
处理，所以有些事情会发生
be very different notably this is not
非常不同，这不是
based on or doesn't and does not require
基于或不需要，不需要
the servlet api it uses a brand-new web
servlet API，它使用全新的网络
runtime called based on any that we
运行时基于任何我们调用的
built now you can you can run the spring
现在建造，你可以运行弹簧
webflix api on top of a servlet through
通过servlet之上的webflix api
that one or better environment and
一个或更佳的环境
that'll be it'll be Oh
就是那样哦
in certain certain cases but of course
在某些情况下，当然
there are some parts of the servlet API
Servlet API的某些部分
that are inherently blocking and there's
本质上是阻塞的，
just nothing we can do about that so
我们对此无能为力
while will you have a facade on top of
而你会在
it and while it does work fine for the
它，虽然它确实适用于
request and response in this case some
在这种情况下的请求和响应
parts of the API some corners API will
API的某些部分，一些角落API将会
not be truly reactive in even though
即使，即使
we've got the the our abstraction on top
我们的顶层是我们的抽象
of it but this is a nice feature of
但这是一个不错的功能
string well flex which is that you get
字符串好flex这是你得到
the portability you could run this on
您可以在其上运行的可移植性
top of something like WebSphere now I
现在像WebSphere这样的东西我
don't necessarily recommend that you do
不一定建议您这样做
that and of course but the point is you
那，当然，但是重点是你
could if you need to but you'll find
可以，如果您需要，但您会发现
that we're actually using a and you know
我们实际上使用的是
there's an eddy but walking in any
有一个漩涡，但是走在任何地方
context here that's being split up for
这里的上下文被拆分为
you by default so let's put an endpoint
您默认情况下，让我们放置一个端点
here we're gonna say public by ID and
在这里，我们要通过ID和
this will be I'll take a movie ID and
这是我要带的电影ID，
we're just gonna delegate to the service
我们只是委托给服务
there so there's that and of course this
在那里，当然有这个
is a web endpoints I'll get mapping
是我要映射的网络端点
movies curly braket ID and this becomes
电影卷曲刹车ID，这变成
a path variable alright so we want to
好的路径变量，所以我们想
have that one have an endpoint here that
在那有一个终点
return is just all the movies right
返回就是所有电影的权利
there's that so fun all equals MS all
有那么有趣，都等于MS全部
good and we want to have one more
好，我们希望再有一个
endpoint that returns the data coming
返回数据的端点
back from the from the event in play
从比赛进行中返回
from the event service so we're gonna
来自活动服务，所以我们要
say movies ID events now this would seem
说电影ID事件，现在看来
to be fairly straightforward I think but
我认为很简单
there's a bit of a problem with this
这个有点问题
code isn't there like imagine I wrote
代码不像我想象的那样存在
this code imagine I run this code what's
这段代码想象我运行这段代码是什么
gonna happen write this code but at
会写这段代码，但在
fault we're gonna get JSON you know is
错，我们会得到你知道的JSON
the content to go the client is gonna
客户要去的内容
send a except headers that indicate that
发送一个例外标头，指出
we want an application JSON of some
我们想要一些应用程序JSON
sorts of the service will dutifully
各种服务将尽职尽责
respond and it'll send us back Jason but
回应，它将把我们送回杰森，但
of course here you know the client isn't
当然在这里您知道客户不是
prepared for a JSON document that never
为从未使用过的JSON文档做准备
stomps all right this JSON structure is
sto脚，这个JSON结构是
gonna keep going forever and ever and
将永远继续下去，
ever so what what we need to do is to
因此，我们需要做的是
signal to the client now this is data
向客户端发出信号，现在这是数据
that will that will have that will never
那将永远不会
never terminate and if it's a client
永远不要终止，如果它是一个客户
knows of the protocol of the of the
知道的协议
content type you know it'll do the right
您知道的内容类型将正确处理
thing so we need to give it a clue as to
东西，所以我们需要给它一个线索
what its gonna as what's gonna happen we
它会发生什么，我们会发生什么
could we need something that is geared
我们需要适合的东西吗
for this right we could use a number of
为此，我们可以使用许多
gem things we could use WebSockets
我们可以使用WebSockets的宝石
WebSockets are of course a
WebSockets当然是
bi-directional
双向的
protocol allows to push down date it
协议允许下推日期
down to the client so it as long as the
下到客户，所以只要
client has a socket open it'll expect to
客户端打开了一个套接字，它将期望
receive new data and it'll it'll cycle
接收新数据，它将循环
back to the client is flying fast as
回到客户飞得很快
possible and that's certainly easy
可能，那当然很容易
enough to do there's a spring tips
足以做一个春天的提示
install minute video I just recorded a
安装我刚刚录制的分钟录像
few weeks ago on that exact topic on
几周前关于
using the reactive WebSocket support
使用反应式WebSocket支持
spring from five but for our purposes
从五点开始，但出于我们的目的
it's simple enough to just signal that
这很简单，只需发出信号
we're going to be producing data that
我们将要产生的数据
supports service and events so what I'm
支持服务和事件，所以我
going to do is here is I'm gonna say
我要做的是在这里说
send back the media type for text event
发回文本事件的媒体类型
streaming values okay so there's our our
流值好，所以我们的
rest endpoint plus one extra type of
其余端点，再加上一种
endpoint that supports server sent
支持服务器的端点已发送
events so let's go ahead and restart the
事件，让我们继续并重新启动
service
服务
open up the browser here now
现在在这里打开浏览器
one thing that's peculiar about what's
一件事是什么奇特的
happening here is that as I'm because
发生在这里是因为我是因为
I'm recording this computer's crawling
我正在记录这台计算机的爬网
just sluggish so curl HTTP localhost
只是呆滞所以卷曲HTTP本地主机
8080 forward slash movies okay there's
8080前斜线电影好吗
our records right and we can see they're
我们的记录正确，我们可以看到它们是
all there now we can look for a
现在所有的我们都可以寻找
particular record here let's just grab
这里的特定记录让我们来抓
this ID copy curl let's grab that one
这个ID副本卷曲让我们抓住那个
there we go okay
那里我们可以
there's that single record great that
那个唱片很棒
seems to be okay and there is
似乎还可以，并且有
something wrong with that let's see
让我们看看有什么问题
you
您
oops forgot to specify the path variable
oops忘记指定路径变量
for the events endpoint so let's try
对于事件端点，让我们尝试
that again
再次
now the error you saw was that the
现在您看到的错误是
parameter was specified as non null and
参数指定为非null和
of course it was sent to us as null and
当然它是作为null发送给我们的，
I was actually
我当时
that's a nice the language itself signal
语言本身的信号很好
that it's supposed to be not null so we
它应该不为空，所以我们
got NEX epsilon into that so there's our
有了NEX epsilon，所以我们
movies and here's the parameter
电影，这是参数
there's the events there we are there's
有事件，我们在那里
our different data being sent back to
我们将不同的数据发送回
the client now this is using message
客户端现在正在使用消息
framing you can see that each each new
可以看到每个新
record is deleted by a data colon
记录由数据冒号删除
purpose and then a new line and a new
目的，然后再换一条新线
line at the as a subject so we have now
行作为主题，所以我们现在有
our endpoint now this is certainly one
我们的终点现在肯定是一个
way to write the endpoint it's fine if
编写端点的方法，如果
you're coming from spring WebM you see
您来自春季WebM，您会看到
this will feel very familiar but there
这会感觉很熟悉，但是在那里
is a new endpoint that we could use here
是我们可以在此处使用的新端点
as well so I'm going to build a new
以及，所以我要建立一个新的
endpoint using the functional reactive
使用功能性反应的端点
support in spring web flex I'm gonna say
我会说Spring Web Flex的支持
web configuration and we're going to
网络配置，我们将
inject the movie service here I guess we
我想在这里注入电影服务
don't need the file in your bar well
不需要酒吧里的文件
okay I'll enter and so this is a
好吧，我进入，所以这是一个
configuration class it's a spring it's a
配置类是春天，是春天
class that will produce beans it's a
会产生豆子的类
bean provider if you will so I'm going
bean提供者，如果你愿意，我要去
to include bean provider that produces a
包括产生一个
set of routes so here we could use the
一组路线，所以在这里我们可以使用
router function
路由器功能
type from from spring webflix and
从spring webflix输入
someone we could do all that and create
我们可以做的所有事情并创造
a request predicate and and so on but um
一个请求谓词，依此类推，但是
we don't really need to do all this
我们真的不需要做所有这一切
right there's actually a you know the
其实有一个你知道的
final parameter here is a handler
最后的参数是一个处理程序
function and if you had provided I have
功能，如果您提供的话，我有
a function that would be enough but this
一个功能就足够了，但这
is the Java API there's actually a
是Java API，实际上
Kotlin native DSL in spring framing
春季框架中的Kotlin原生DSL
itself right so it's already on the
本身是正确的，所以它已经在
class map all we have to do is to use
类图，我们要做的就是使用
the router DSL here so we say router and
这里是路由器DSL，所以我们说路由器和
we can describe some interactions so the
我们可以描述一些相互作用，所以
first endpoint is called movies and it's
第一个端点叫做电影，它是
expecting and lambda here on the set on
在这里期待和lambda
the other side so we could have lambda
另一面，所以我们可以有lambda
and again I could create a lambda that
然后我可以创建一个lambda
has the parameter I could acknowledge
具有我可以确认的参数
that but I don't need that parameter so
那但是我不需要那个参数所以
there's no point and it'll be given to
没有意义，它将给予
me it has an implicit parameter anyway
我仍然有一个隐式参数
so what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna say
所以我要说的是
when somebody asks for all the movies
当有人要所有的电影
I'm going to use the router service I'm
我将使用路由器服务
sorry the movie service that I've got
对不起，我得到的电影服务
there I'm gonna say server response
在那里我要说服务器响应
that's ok dot body equals M S dot all
没关系，点体等于全部MS点
and I have to specify here for the
我必须在这里指定
second parameter the type of data that
第二个参数的数据类型
we're sending back to the client so
我们正在发回客户，所以
classic Java that is our one handler
经典的Java是我们的一个处理程序
right we can duplicate that for the
对，我们可以复制
other three endpoints here so let's see
其他三个端点，让我们来看一下
movies ID and here we're gonna say give
电影ID，在这里我们要说给
me a record by ID and I can just say it
给我一个ID记录，我可以说
got path variable where where it of
得到路径变量在哪里
course is this in this case is the
当然是这种情况
request and here I want to get the movie
请求，在这里我想看电影
events I'll change this to be a movie
事件，我将其更改为电影
event
事件
and this will be events and we'll say it
这将是事件，我们会说
got path variable equals idea now
现在得到的路径变量等于想法
we have is a that second parameter is
我们有一个第二个参数是
telling the right web runtime what type
告诉合适的Web运行时什么类型
of data we're sending back so consider
我们要发回的数据，因此请考虑
what's happening here
这里发生了什么事
we're sending back sending back data
我们正在发回数据
that may be you know potentially very
可能是您非常了解
large in the last case it's never ending
在最后的情况下，它永远不会结束
and the first two it could be billions
前两个可能是数十亿
of movies not that there aren't billing
的电影不是没有帐单
now there are billion movies I guess but
我猜现在有十亿部电影
but it could be it's my point the
但这可能是我的观点
runtime has no idea and so it needs to
运行时不知道，所以需要
know when de to frame the message and
知道何时将消息框起来
then sort of send it back to the client
然后将其发送回客户端
right so it needs to eat out as many
对，所以它需要吃掉很多
count and emit as many values as it can
计数并发出尽可能多的值
whatever whatever opportunity it gets so
不管机会如何
what we need to do is we need to give it
我们需要做的就是给它
a clue as to when to do that right so I
关于何时正确执行操作的线索，所以我
forgot to give that a content type so we
忘了给那个内容类型，所以我们
need to give it a clue as to when to do
需要提供有关何时执行的线索
that we're telling it to do so every
我们告诉它做到这一点
time it finds a record that can be
找到记录的时间
considered a movie or a movie event in
被视为电影或电影事件
the case of the lab the last end point
实验室情况下的最后一个终点
there and we're doing that explicitly
在那里，我们正在明确地这样做
here because it has no way of figuring
在这里，因为它没有办法
that out from the response from the
从回应中
values that get sent in from the service
从服务发送来的值
right the MS done events MS dot by ID
正确的MS完成的事件MS点按ID
etc it doesn't know because at runtime
等不知道，因为在运行时
you know in the JDK in the JVM genetic
您知道在JDK中的JVM遗传
planners are lost so we we need to be
规划师迷路了，所以我们需要
explicit about that right so we're
明确的权利，所以我们
telling it this is a a publisher of type
告诉它这是类型的发布商
movie and so every movie you can send
电影，因此您可以发送的每部电影
back the data alright now let's go back
返回数据，现在让我们返回
to our console here I can say curl HTTP
到我们的控制台，我可以说curl HTTP
localhost 8080 forward slash movies good
本地主机8080正斜杠电影好
you
您
and paste and we go then
然后粘贴，然后我们去
10 points there we are there's the same
我们那里有10点相同
service we implemented using the
我们使用
function reactive endpoints now which
现在功能反应性端点
one should you use well it's Internet up
你应该很好地使用它的一个互联网
to you I think right a lot of people
对你我想很多人
like this style and if you've ever used
喜欢这种风格，如果您曾经使用过
Sinatra on the Ruby on Rails role or
Sinatra担任Ruby on Rails角色或
scotch or spark Java
苏格兰威士忌或火花
this might be more familiar to you if
如果您对此更熟悉
you're coming from spring MVC this might
您来自春季MVC，这可能
be more familiar to you
对你更熟悉
whatever style you like we don't you
无论您喜欢哪种风格，我们都不是
know we don't have a strong opinion this
知道我们对此没有强烈的意见
just seems to be a very useful thing to
似乎是一件非常有用的事情
have and this sort of reactive
有这种反应
functional reactive world alright so we
功能性反应世界还不错，所以我们
now have a web application talking to
现在有一个Web应用程序正在与
the Internet
互联网
we have data we're talking to the data
我们有数据，我们正在与数据对话
tier this is still at the end of the day
直到今天结束
just a toy I think however because we've
我认为只是一个玩具，因为我们
kind of ignored some of the very real
有点忽略了一些非常真实的
concerns that people have to care about
人们必须关心的问题
when they move to this approach so one
当他们转向这种方法时，
thing that we care about when we move to
我们搬到这里时关心的事情
this you know to when we move an
当我们移动一个
application to production is
应用于生产是
observability I wanna be able to
可观察性我想
understand what the application is doing
了解应用程序在做什么
I wanna be able to service information
我想能够提供信息
about the application so that I can
关于应用程序，以便我可以
monitor it I can inspect it at one time
监视它，我可以一次检查它
and so I have neglected in this case to
所以我在这种情况下忽略了
bring in a library from spring boot
从春季启动带进图书馆
called the spring boot starter actuator
称为弹簧启动启动器执行器
so I'll bring in an actuator
所以我带一个执行器
an actuator is not a new thing it has
执行器不是新事物
nothing there's nothing new about it or
没有什么没有什么新的或者
specific to the reactive support except
特定于反应性支持物，除了
that it was previously written in terms
它以前是用术语写的
of the spring MVC
春季MVC的
web runtime right and so that that
Web运行时正确，这样
support is now available for spring web
现在支持Spring Web
flux and indeed it's also available for
通量，实际上它也可用于
jax-rs so you'll see that it that's a
jax-rs，所以您会看到它是一个
nice feature that the actuator end
执行器端的一个不错的功能
points have been decoupled from the the
点已与
web runtime that's in play here so it's
Web运行时在这里发挥作用
game it could be spring mu C can be
游戏可能是春季亩C
spring one flex or it could be jax-rs
弹簧一弯曲或它可能是jax-rs
so okay there's our spring boot actuator
好吧，我们的弹簧启动器
we're gonna we're gonna activate it by
我们将通过以下方式激活它
using this property endpoints to disable
使用此属性端点禁用
that or the importance default we have
或我们拥有的重要性默认值
been able to goes true we can run the
能够实现，我们可以运行
code here but before I do I also want to
代码在这里，但在我这样做之前，我也想
address security right this is another
解决安全问题，这是另一个
concern that we have to care about
我们必须关心的问题
production environment so I'm gonna go
生产环境，所以我要去
back to my build and I'll bring in
回到我的建筑，我将带来
spring boot starter with security
具有安全性的Spring Boot Starter
reactive okay so there is this
反应性好，所以有这个
and we're not going to do too much to
而且我们不会做太多的事情
make this work you could do all sorts
使这项工作可以做各种事情
you know spring security has at its
你知道春天的安全
heart the concept of an authentication
心认证的概念
manager and and then on the other side
经理，然后在另一边
it has an authorization manager
它有一个授权管理器
basically something like that and these
基本上是这样的
two interfaces handle authentication and
两个接口处理身份验证和
authorization respectively if we set up
如果我们成立，分别授权
a default if we set up an object of type
如果我们设置类型的对象，则为默认值
user details repository spring security
用户详细信息存储库Spring Security
we'll assume that we want to talk to
我们假设我们想和
whatever data access layer based
基于任何数据访问层
repository object that we give it to
我们给它的存储库对象
answer questions about users that are
回答有关用户的问题
coming in and making requests into the
进入并向其中提出要求
system and it'll automatically lock down
系统，它将自动锁定
everything using HTTP basic so
一切都使用HTTP基本，所以
authorization will be done automatically
授权将自动完成
if it's a you know if it's authenticated
如果是，您知道它是否已通过身份验证
it goes through otherwise it's not and
它经历了否则，不是
it'll be H to be basic you can configure
基本可以配置为H
that in more detail but since we're
更详细地说，但由于我们
short on time I'll leave that to your
时间短，我会留给你
imagination so let's just do some basic
想像力，让我们做一些基本的
basic spring security here basic spring
基本的弹簧安全在这里基本的弹簧
security five it's good we're gonna say
安全五，我们要说的很好
we want to enable web flex security I'm
我们要启用Web Flex安全性
going to create a beam endpoint are
要创建光束端点
being definition that describes our
是描述我们的定义
users and again we're gonna use that you
用户，我们将再次使用您
know the user details repository
知道用户详细信息存储库
abstraction that spring security five is
春季安全五是的抽象
looking for here right this is Maps more
在这里寻找，这是Maps more
or less to the user details service in
或更少的用户详细信息服务
classic spring security in synchronous
同步中的经典Spring Security
blocking spring security so we've
阻止春季安全，所以我们已经
reworked a lot of things in the reactor
重做了反应堆中的很多东西
spring security support to allow it to
春季安全支持，使其能够
work in this world because think about
在这个世界上工作是因为思考
it but that's putting that you want to
它，但这就是你想要的
do is have all this beautiful reactive
要做的就是让所有这些美丽的反应
code only to be deadlocked at a at a
代码只能在a处死锁
thread local right blocking synchronous
线程本地权限阻塞同步
thread local where of course that makes
本地线程当然使
very little sense in the reactor world
在反应堆世界上几乎没有意义
so we're gonna say that the user name is
所以我们要说用户名是
our winch for of course the one and only
我们的绞车当然是唯一的
Rob winch in need of spring security
Rob Winch需要弹簧保护
we're gonna have a give him the role of
我们要给他一个角色
admin and user of course and go better
管理员和用户当然会更好
now I can also build another user here
现在我也可以在这里建立另一个用户
with his name J along dot password
他的名字J和点密码
equals PW that roles equals just user
等于角色等于用户的PW
and what
还有什么
that one as well all right so there
那一个还好吧
we've got we've got two hard-coded users
我们有两个硬编码用户
the user details repository the contract
用户详细信息存储库合同
is very simple it is just you know given
很简单，就是你知道
a username returned a publisher of type
用户名返回了类型的发布者
user details right and so there's our
正确的用户详细信息，所以我们有
simple user details repository that
简单的用户详细信息存储库
we're returning when spring security is
我们将在春季安全保护期回来
activated that'll be used to lock down
已激活，将用于锁定
the system so let's go ahead and run
系统，让我们继续运行
this code again
再次输入此代码
now we could at any point we could
现在我们可以在任何时候
configure another beam that returns an
配置另一个返回
HP security filter basically and that
惠普安全过滤器的基本原理
would give us the ability to configure
将使我们能够进行配置
authorization but for our purposes it's
授权，但出于我们的目的，
fine to leave it as it is as I say so
可以按我说的那样保留它
that's good a shell and we'll say it
贝壳很好，我们会说
curl HTTP localhost 8080 four slash
curl HTTP本地主机8080四个斜杠
movies now I'm gonna I'm gonna do is I'm
电影现在我要去做
going to go to the beginning here I'll
我要去这里开始
say I want to see there for both results
说我想看到两个结果
okay and so there you go it says 401
好的，所以你去那里说401
unauthorized right we need to
未经授权的权利，我们需要
authenticate that's fair
验证那是公平的
so go to the beginning we're going to
所以从头开始，我们要
specify - you that's the username and
指定-您的用户名和
password for for curl command and the
curl命令的密码和
user will be J long and the password
用户将为J long，密码为
will be PW and there we are if we do
将是PW，如果存在，我们就在那
that and pipe that out to Jason P P we
然后将其发送给Jason PP，我们
can see who we get the JSON data right
可以看到谁正确地获得了JSON数据
so there's no there's no error as well
所以没有错误也没有
so that works now one of the other
所以现在可以工作
things that we just added
我们刚刚添加的内容
were those actuator endpoints now as I
现在是那些执行器端点
say actuator serves a very common goal
说执行器有一个很共同的目标
you see it doesn't matter which
你看哪一个都没关系
organization you are doesn't matter what
组织你是什么都没关系
technology stack you're using doesn't
您使用的技术堆栈没有
matter where in the world you are and
无论您身在何处，
what business vertical you're in one
您属于哪个行业
thing seems to be surprised and
事情似乎很惊讶，
consistent when the pager goes off
传呼机关闭时保持一致
somebody gets roused to a computer and
有人被计算机唤醒
has to figure out what's going on their
必须弄清楚他们的情况
job is not lose root cause analysis
工作不失根源分析
their job is to triage whatever is
他们的工作是分类
happening and stop the bleeding right so
发生并阻止出血，所以
everything we can do in those waning
我们在衰落中能做的一切
seconds and the dead of morning to help
秒和早晨的死帮助
that process along is valuable so sir
那个过程很有价值，先生
the actuator serves that goal it
执行器达到了目标
surfaces information about the
表面有关的信息
application and while you can get well
应用程序，虽然你会好起来
there are a lot of the number of other
还有很多其他的
sources that you can get inside about
您可以了解的资源
your application there is nothing better
您的应用程序没有比这更好的了
than your application itself to to
比您的应用程序本身要
articulate that state so here you can
阐明该状态，以便在这里您可以
see we have an actuator you know a
看到我们有一个执行器，您知道
health check let's write that out to
健康检查，让我们写出来
JSON as well and the health check told
JSON以及运行状况检查
me my my connection to my TV it tells me
我，我与电视的连接告诉我
about my filesystem connection and it so
关于我的文件系统连接及其相关信息
it shows me that these things are up and
它告诉我这些事情已经发生，
if they weren't up and of course the
如果他们没有起来，当然
status of my application itself or be
我的应用程式本身的状态或
imperiled and we'd see that reflected
陷入困境，我们会看到这一点
here would say status equals down I
这里会说地位等于我
won't spend too long on the actuator
不会花太长时间在执行器上
points but surprise it to say there's a
点，但惊讶地说有一个
whole number of them and they all work
他们的总数，他们都工作
nicely in a reactive world now
现在在反应良好的世界中
all right so we've got a secure reactive
好的，所以我们有一个安全的反应
observable application that's got a Web
具有Web的可观察应用程序
API we looked at two ways to write the
API我们研究了两种编写方法
API and it's talking to a data tier and
API，它正在与数据层和
we also looked at reactor but this
我们还看了反应堆，但这
wouldn't be much of a service without a
没有一个服务就不会有太多服务
client so let's go back to IntelliJ and
客户，让我们回到IntelliJ和
let's build a new client module so
让我们建立一个新的客户端模块
create a new project next I'm gonna call
接下来要创建一个新项目
this the flux flix client we'll use
我们将使用的这个flux flix客户端
let's use Java this time there's no
这次使用Java
reason not to it doesn't you know both
不这样做的原因你们俩​​都不知道吗
are nice languages then it will both
是好的语言，那么两者都会
work just fine of course so hit next and
当然工作正常，所以接下来点击
we're just going to use reactive web
我们只是要使用反应式网络
right so here we are
对，所以我们在这里
oops
哎呀
for a reactive web
用于反应性网
it next
接下来
finish new window alright so the first
完成新窗口好，所以第一个
thing that we need to do this of course
我们当然需要做的事情
to move this to a separate port so we're
将其移动到单独的端口，所以我们
gonna say serve it up port equals 80 81
要说送达端口等于80 81
and I'm gonna use the Flex fix client
我将使用Flex修复客户端
application Java and here all we're
应用Java，这就是我们
gonna do is just create a a client so
要做的就是创建一个客户，这样
we're gonna create a web client to talk
我们将创建一个网络客户端以进行交谈
to the service and we could use the
服务，我们可以使用
spring frame equal rest template write
弹簧框架平等休息模板写
the rest template is certainly a
其余模板肯定是
interesting option here but the problem
有趣的选择，但是问题
is that the rest of it is is synchronous
是其余的是同步的
it's and it blocks and it's not
是的，它阻止了，不是
particularly geared for unlimited
特别适合无限
amounts of data this would be a very
大量的数据，这将是一个非常
hard thing to to manage we could call
我们很难打电话来管理
those first two weapon points with you
你的前两个武器要点
know not too much trouble assuming
知道没有太多麻烦
there's not too much data but we'd have
没有太多的数据，但我们有
we'd run into trouble when we call the
我们打电话给我们时会遇到麻烦
last one the yeah service and event
最后一项是的服务和活动
endpoint so let's create a yeah let's
终结点，所以让我们创建一个耶
use the new web client that's induced in
使用引入的新的Web客户端
spring web clicks I'm gonna create a web
春季网络点击，我将创建一个网络
client and I'm gonna you know prefix all
客户，我会知道所有前缀
of its calls to 80 84 slash movies and
拨打了80 84部斜线电影，
we want to mutate it we want to mutate
我们想要变异它我们想要变异
it because we want to configure a filter
因为我们要配置一个过滤器
right so so I'm gonna say exchange
对，所以我要说交换
filter function but whoops
过滤功能，但是
you
您
good
好
filter well tie
过滤网
you
您
I have done something
我做了点事
let's see here cat desktop mask on Lux
让我们在这里看到Lux上的猫桌面面具
Lux client source main column I just
勒克斯客户端源主要专栏我只是
wrote this code
写下这段代码
or so I know that exchange filter
或者我知道那个交换过滤器
functions basic authentication that
具有基本身份验证功能
should be all we need
应该是我们所需要的
let's see alright ah there we go
让我们看看好啊，我们去了
I should have created first okay so get
我应该先创建好吧
rid of that there we are now we're
摆脱那里，我们现在我们在
cooking so what we're doing is we're
做饭，所以我们正在做的是
saying we want to create a new web
说我们要创建一个新的网站
client client we're going to preface all
客户我们将为所有客户做序
the requests to localhost 8080 movies
对本地主机8080电影的请求
and win a creative filter that does
并赢得了
basic authentication for Geelong and PW
Geelong和PW的基本身份验证
now we're gonna use that client here in
现在我们要在这里使用该客户端
our application runners I'm gonna say
我们要说的应用程序赛跑者
application runner runner I'm gonna
我要去的应用程序赛跑者
inject the web client as a parameter
将Web客户端作为参数注入
here right so what we're gonna do is
在这里，所以我们要做的是
we're gonna say web client dot git dot
我们要说网络客户点git dot
your I equals and of course there's
你我等于，当然有
nothing to get right we're just gonna
没有什么是正确的，我们只是要
call all the records we're gonna
打电话给我们所有的记录
retrieve the data we're going to turn it
检索我们将要翻转的数据
into a type of movie so I'm gonna say
变成一部电影，所以我要说
class movie private and of course here
私人电影课，当然在这里
benefits us it benefits us to have
对我们有利，对我们有益
Lombok right so I should have added that
龙目岛对，所以我应该补充一点
to the class path thankfully we already
上课的道路幸好我们已经
got the Lombok plug-in sold so all I
卖了龙目岛插件，所以我
need to do is to add that to the class
需要做的是将其添加到类中
path and I can say add data
路径，我可以说添加数据
and I'll say on private string ID
我会说说私人字符串ID
private string title and this will
私有字符串标题，这将
create an all argument constructor and a
创建一个全参数构造函数和一个
no argument constructor alright so
没有参数构造函数，所以
there's our our basic type and we also
这是我们的基本类型，我们也
want a type to describe the movie event
想要一种类型来描述电影事件
right so I'll say we have a movie event
对，所以我要说我们有电影活动
and this will be a it'll have a string
这将是一个它将有一个字符串
called the movie ID and a date called
称为电影ID，日期称为
date
日期
there we are so there's our basic
我们在那里，这是我们的基本
structures from that service side for
该服务方面的结构
the implementation and we're just
实施，我们只是
creating a details and the client here
在此处创建详细信息和客户
so we can have something to with which
这样我们就可以
to work I'm gonna say I want the body of
工作，我要说我想要身体
all the requests to come back as a movie
所有要求返回电影的请求
class and we'll in a filter a particular
类，我们将在过滤器中
movie I want to say give me the title
我想说的电影给我标题
and if the title contains one of these
如果标题包含以下内容之一
movies let's see
看电影
we can say I want that and then we want
我们可以说我想要那个然后我们想要
a flat map that one with one result and
一张平面图，结果是一个
turn that into another call to the
把它变成另一个呼叫
events in point right so ID events
点事件，因此ID事件
passing in of course the ID itself in
当然传入ID本身
the movie and then we want to turn that
电影，然后我们想把它
into a request that we then turn into a
变成一个要求，然后我们变成一个
body of flux so type movie event up
助焊剂的主体，所以键入电影事件
class and
类和
let's see it what's wrong with that so
让我们看看这是怎么回事
we're gonna sell yeah this is the year
我们要卖的是今年
your I body to I turn a args
你我的身体乱搞我变成一个args
alright and then finally of course we
好吧，最后当然我们
want to subscribe so when I say call the
想订阅，所以当我说致电
system.out.print line method each time
每次使用system.out.print行方法
there's a new record that gets returned
有一条新记录被退回
from that so let's now run this code
从那开始，让我们现在运行这段代码
here now when this runs we should
现在，当这运行时，我们应该
hopefully see that it's making a request
希望看到它正在发出请求
and authenticated it should be basic
并验证它应该是基本的
authenticated request to the
认证请求
localhost:8080 movies endpoint and then
localhost：8080电影端点，然后
it's gonna get the data find the
它会得到数据找到
particular record that were interested
感兴趣的特定记录
in and then stream the the movie events
然后播放电影事件
as we have them in a server-side and
因为我们将它们放在服务器端
there we are so with that my friends
在那里我们和我的朋友们在一起
we've got just a few seconds maybe six
我们只有几秒钟，也许是六秒钟
seconds and so we're at the top of the
秒，所以我们位于顶部
hour we've looked at reactor River that
一个小时，我们看了反应堆河
spring Webb flux we've looked at the
春季韦伯助焊剂，我们已经看过
function reactive endpoints we looked at
我们研究的功能反应性端点
these spring NEC style endpoints we
这些春季NEC风格的终结点
looked at spring data we looked at
看了我们看过的春季数据
spring security we looked at the
春季安全我们看了
actuator support and we looked at how to
执行器支持，我们研究了如何
build a web client
建立一个网络客户端
there's also fully integrated testing
还有完全集成的测试
support and also let me reiterate this
支持，让我重申一下
is just the beginning the release of
仅仅是发布的开始
spring frameworks five has already set
春季框架已经设定了五个
off a series of dominoes of new releases
一系列新发行的多米诺骨牌
all integrating their official sort of
全部整合他们的官方
Spring Framework five support so we've
Spring Framework五种支持，因此我们已经
been working on this this has been in
一直在为此工作
the works for more than a year for most
对于大多数人来说，工作超过一年
of these projects and so we're you know
这些项目，所以我们你知道
you're gonna see a lot of new releases
你会看到很多新版本
coming up in the and the weeks and
在和几周内
months ahead and of course spring mood
未来数月，当然还有春天的心情
to to dyno will in turn allow us to
到dyno将反过来使我们能够
release new release of spring cloud
发行Spring Cloud的新版​​本
spring cloud Finchley in the next and
春季云Finchley和
the first quarter we think of of 2018
我们想到的第一季度2018
spring cloud has a new technology called
春云有一项新技术叫做
spring spring card gateway which in turn
spring弹簧卡网关
builds on the reactive support here so
建立在这里的反应性支持上
we can do a lot of amazing things now
我们现在可以做很多很棒的事情
that we're at we have a Java 8 and
我们有一个Java 8，
lambda a friendly baseline now that we
现在，lambda是一个友好的基准
have the reactive support in Spring
在春季获得反应性支持
Break Spring Framework five as a
将Spring Framework打破5
foundation and and we hope that you'll
基金会，我们希望您能
take advantage of it I want to thank you
利用它，我要谢谢你
so much for all your time
这么多的时间
and answer questions and you know don't
并回答问题，你知道不
hesitate to reach out to me in spine and
毫不犹豫地与我联系
Twitter ahead Starbucks man if you have
Twitter领先星巴克，如果有的话
questions comments or feedback otherwise
问题评论或反馈
Andrea I think pass it back to you my
安德里亚，我想把它还给我
friend
朋友
thank you George splendid it was so
谢谢你，乔治如此出色
impressive I didn't even expect you to
令人印象深刻，我什至没想到你会
make it in caught them so I'm so happy
赶上他们，所以我很高兴
we have a couple of questions please
我们有几个问题请
only too well so first very many
太好了，所以首先很多
questions what is what makes reactive
问题是什么使反应性
security reactive yeah so this is a
安全反应性是的，所以这是一个
great question the reactive security
被动安全问题
stuff we have contact propagation we had
我们有接触传播的东西
to change the way we do context
改变背景的方式
propagation and so that is a major part
传播，所以这是主要部分
of the reworking and then basically
返工，然后基本上
we've reworked some of the core
我们重新设计了一些核心
interfaces to now work in terms of
现在可以使用的界面
publishers so the where we can we
出版商，所以我们可以在哪里
produce the author the authentication
向作者出示认证
manager basically we produce that
经理，基本上我们生产
asynchronously we produce things like
异步地我们产生像
the user details repository as a
用户详细信息存储库为
publisher these things are values these
发布者这些东西是这些价值观
are values that we don't need to have on
是我们不需要的价值观
demand when we first initialize and we
我们第一次初始化时的需求
don't need to have necessarily even
不必一定要偶
until later on in the processing
直到以后处理
pipeline so we defer until last moment
流水线，所以我们推迟到最后一刻
when this information becomes available
当此信息可用时
so there's a number of different things
所以有很多不同的事情
there I don't purport to understand all
那里我并不是想了解所有
of what's happening there I just know
我知道那里发生的一切
that there's a lot of work that has to
有很多工作要做
be done to unwind some of the defaults
完成一些默认设置
blocking assumptions and also of course
阻碍假设，当然
this works in a string web flex world so
这适用于字符串web flex世界
we've reworked spring security to to
我们将弹簧安全性重新设计为
work with the new filter model to work
与新的过滤器模型一起工作
with the processing lifecycle of the
与处理生命周期
spring one flex runs on because remember
春天一号继续运行，因为记住
this is not a servlet based application
这不是基于servlet的应用程序
whereas a lot of the existing sort of
而许多现有的
fundamental stuff that you just worked
您刚刚工作过的基本内容
with and it's pretty secured in before
并在之前非常安全
wouldn't have worked in it you know it
你不会知道的
required the server the API okay next
下一步需要服务器API
question can we use cut encourages to
问题我们可以用削减鼓励
avoid avoid spaghetti code so before you
避免避免意大利面代码，所以在您之前
command that there is a third party
命令有第三方
project called spring coddling
春季拥抱项目
coroutines bio notes Kaminsky
协程生物笔记Kaminsky
used at Allegro and well but for
用于Allegro和很好，但用于
official comments yeah I think it's
官方评论是的，我认为是
better to ask Josh well so we don't have
最好问乔希好吧，所以我们没有
anything right now but I think I saw
现在有什么，但我想我看到了
rumblings of discussions about
关于的讨论隆隆
supporting that in in reactor itself
在反应堆本身中支持
right so that as a research thing so
对，这样作为研究的东西
that's certainly something I've seen you
那肯定是我见过你的东西
talked about recently it's not there yet
谈到最近还没有
but maybe that third party party might
但也许第三方可能
be interesting I don't know cool there's
有趣的是，我不知道很酷
a comment about the IDE support what
关于IDE支持的评论
extra plugins
额外的插件
does Josh use I could not find spring 5
乔希用我找不到 spring 5
support so well first of all spring 5
首先，春天这么好支持5
support Israel in the latest release and
在最新版本中支持以色列，并
also in the of course the new one which
当然还有新的
is a preview but since Josh is Scotland
是一个预览，但由于乔希是苏格兰
well so the idea for depends on the
好吧，这个主意取决于
support for coding along with spring and
支持编码以及spring和
this is partially already available in
这已经部分可用
the Latsis latest release but it's more
Latsis最新版本，但更多
to come in in the in the point three
进入第三点
release which is coming in one month
一个月后发布
right yeah I didn't have to use I loved
是的，我不必使用我爱的
intelligent great tool but let's be
智能伟大的工具，但让我们成为
pretty frank here this is just basic
坦率地说，这只是基本
Java and you know public static void
Java，您知道public static void
main and I used almost nothing the
主要，我几乎什么也没用
Lombok plugin int is that that's a great
Lombok插件int很棒
plugin for the Java code for the
Java代码的插件
Cartland side I use the impressive
卡特兰方面我印象深刻
support for Cartland built into IntelliJ
支持IntelliJ中内置的Cartland
although you know I give I give the the
虽然你知道我给我给
folks a trip rains a lot of credit they
乡亲们下雨了很多功劳
also built a pretty good kauffman plugin
还构建了一个非常不错的kauffman插件
for Eclipse isn't that right yeah so a
对于Eclipse来说不是很正确，所以
lot of this is it just worked just
这很多，它只是工作而已
worked perfectly
工作完美
next question about spring clouds and
下一个关于春天云的问题
spring data cloud does it well
Spring数据云做得很好
thus rated Springs for them or those are
因此为他们或那些额定弹簧
different concepts so spring cloud is
不同的概念，所以春天的云是
being reworked to support wherever
重新设计以支持任何地方
possible the reactive work that we've
可能是我们所做的反应性工作
just demonstrated this last hour so
刚刚展示了最后一个小时，所以
spring card will support it we
弹簧卡将支持我们
do have some support for example there
确实有一些支持，例如
is you can already return our job
你已经可以返回我们的工作了吗
observable for example so there's that
例如可以观察到的
that's our external one I think I'm not
那是我们的外部，我认为我不是
sure metrics are Java - there's initial
确保指标是Java-有初步的
preliminary support you can look at the
初步的支持可以看一下
list bills of spring cloud Finchley so
列出春季云Finchley的票据
spring clubs in Chile is not general
智利的春季俱乐部并不普遍
availability yet right it will be as I
可用性，但它会和我一样
say q1 up next year and we have we even
说明年第一季度，我们甚至
have a brand new technology called
有一个叫做
spring cloud gaming which is a gateway
作为门户的春季云游戏
technology that looks and does a lot of
看起来很实用的技术
the same things as as the Zul gateway or
与Zul网关相同或
micro proxy from Netflix but it is built
来自Netflix的微代理，但它是内置的
from the ground up using the spring web
使用弹簧网从头开始
flex runtime so it's reactive and it
flex运行时，所以它是反应性的
will provide a spring centric and spring
将提供弹簧中心和弹簧
friendly component and processing model
友好的组件和处理模型
so there's a lot a lot to admire that in
所以有很多值得佩服的地方
that and I would recommend you to take a
那，我建议你采取一个
look at that so yes it does support
看看那个，是的，它确实支持
reactive support it does support me
反应式支持确实支持我
active programming wherever possible and
主动编程，并尽可能
that's a bit a big part of that is
那是其中很大一部分
making spring boot to nano work cool a
使春季启动纳米工作很酷
slightly related question can I use
我可以使用稍微相关的问题
reactive spring with spring cloud and
弹簧云的反应弹簧和
zoo to build an API gateway is it
动物园要建立一个API网关吗
recommended at all you can use so Zul
推荐所有可以使用的东西，所以祖尔
right now so one that always doesn't
现在，这样一个永远不会
have a reactive API the filter model is
具有反应式API的过滤器模型是
not reactive so I think I think there's
没有反应性，所以我认为我认为
work on that a little too but as far as
也要努力一点
I know that's not quite out there yet is
我知道那还不够
it it could be I don't know I don't know
可能是我不知道我不知道
if he would do that but uh I I know you
如果他愿意那样做，但是我知道你
could do that with with sprinkles anyway
无论如何都可以做到这一点
okay
好的
also if I want to work with a database
另外，如果我想使用数据库
that that doesn't have an icing driver
没有结冰的驱动程序
can I do that implementation using the
我可以使用
block and switch that out when the
封锁并在
database really is the essence River
数据库真的是精华河
yeah I mean you can you can work with
是的，我的意思是你可以和你一起工作
whatever you want but it's up to you to
任何您想要的，但取决于您
now manage
现在管理
moving that work out of the processing
将工作移出处理
loop and and thus far I've kind of just
循环，到目前为止，我有点
looked at the default but it's worth
查看默认值，但值得
understanding it there is actually a
了解它实际上有一个
schedule I so we talked about that ever
安排我，所以我们曾经谈论过
so briefly here there's a scheduler
所以这里有一个调度程序
behind the scenes and that's one of the
在幕后，这是其中之一
knobs and levers that you can you can
可以的旋钮和杠杆
manipulate to to change things so here
设法改变事物，所以在这里
is a publisher and I see it then mini
是出版商，然后我看到它了
that's simply it all schedule whoops
就是所有这些都安排好了
subscribe subscribe
订阅订阅
Oh see that see that subscribe one
哦，看到那个订阅一个
method that says subscribe on and I can
表示订阅的方法，我可以
pass in a scheduler that scheduler can
传递调度程序可以执行的调度程序
be you know schedulers dot any of these
您是否知道调度程序会散布这些
I can print in these are all thread
我可以打印这些都是线程
pools basically executors things like
池基本上是执行者之类的东西
that that you can use to to manage the
您可以用来管理
sort of concurrency of this of this pipe
该管道的这种并发性
of this definition on this pipeline
这个定义在这个管道上
right so you can have more control over
对的，所以您可以更好地控制
how the scheduler moves your work across
调度程序如何跨工作
different threads and so on that's the
不同的线程等等，这就是
nice thing about this is that because
这样做的好处是，因为
we're writing this API we're using this
我们正在编写这个API我们正在使用这个
code and sorry it looks very declarative
代码，对不起，它看起来很声明性
and very imperative we're saying delete
非常重要，我们要说的是删除
then do this then do that then do this
然后做这个然后做那个然后做这个
but there's no you know this doesn't
但是没有你知道这不是
have to be sequential you know there's
必须是连续的，你知道有
nothing about this that is implicitly
对此没有任何暗示
well except for the fact that these are
好，除了这些是
then and then but you can build
然后，但是你可以建立
pipelines that do all sorts of
做各种各样的管道
processing you know and that work can be
处理您知道的工作可以
done in parallel if you if you so Dean
如果您愿意，可以并行完成
it required or necessary well okay the
它是必需的还是必要的，好的
question how we exit spring in line is
问题我们如何在线退出弹簧是
in line with Johanna so reactive spring
符合Johanna的春季反应
right now we Java that Spring Framework
现在我们Java那个Spring框架
five works with Java nine the main
Java的五部作品九篇
feature that we have in Spring Framework
Spring Framework中的功能
five for Java nine is the module this
Java的五个是九个模块
jigsaw right so there's no there's
拼图对，所以没有
nothing specific about the reactive
没有关于反应性的具体说明
support that's that we need to know
我们需要知道的支持
about with respect to Java and I spring
关于Java，我春天
five works just fine it works perfectly
五个作品就很好了
on the module path and on the class path
在模块路径和类路径上
in Gemini that's the that's one of the
在双子座那是其中之一
main features we've also got you know
主要功能我们也让您知道
there's little updates here and there
那里和那里几乎没有更新
for a little you little items in the JDK
在JDK中为您提供一些小项目
that have been updated that we see
我们已经看到更新了
reflected in spring four and five but
反映在春天四五
the main thing that you'll see is that
您将看到的主要内容是
we support the module system now don't
我们现在不支持模块系统
require it mind you but we support it if
要求您介意，但我们会支持
you want it cool
你想要它很酷
well there is a question about IntelliJ
嗯，关于IntelliJ的问题
IDEA if it supports generates test
IDEA是否支持生成测试
methods for Kotlin as it does for job I
Kotlin的方法，就像我的工作一样
believe I believe it does just well but
相信我相信它做得很好，但是
yeah I have to confirm whether in in
是的，我必须确认是否在
case if it doesn't well it's nothing I
情况不好的话我什么都没有
don't think it does
不要以为
I just couldn't unconventional of my
我只是不能让我与众不同
service there and I've got this new
服务在那里，我有这个新
create test method window dialog thing
创建测试方法窗口对话框的东西
and it says which I could create these
它说我可以创建这些
methods and I'm okay sure it okay there
方法，我可以确定那里还可以
we go
我们去
what about cool yeah it works there's a
那很酷，是的，它有一个
well there are some questions which we
好吧，我们有一些问题
can follow up on with the email so I'm
可以跟进电子邮件，所以我
looking for more interest once do you
寻找更多的兴趣一次
have a hint to the people still working
向仍在工作的人们暗示
with my sequel and maybe not sure if we
与我的续集，也许不确定我们是否
kind of come in on that I yeah it's a
有点进来，我是的
it's a it's fine I mean if you you don't
这是很好，我的意思是如果你不
have to use reacts of support but if you
必须使用支持的反应，但是如果您
have a use case where you're doing lots
有一个用例，您在做很多事情
of i/o bound interactions then the
I / O绑定交互，然后
reactor support might be valuable for
反应堆支持可能对
you that said if you're using something
你说如果你正在使用的东西
that's a sequel driver and that's
那是续集的驱动程序，那是
fundamentally blocking and you're okay
从根本上阻止，你还好
with that that's fine too
这样也很好
we're not trying to we're not forcing
我们不试图不强迫
people are moving people forcibly to one
人们将人们强行转移到一个
one import or the other there's a time
一个进口或另一个有一段时间
in a place for these different
在这些不同的地方
technologies there is as I say no
我说没有技术
support right now for JDBC and JPA in
现在支持JDBC和JPA
the reactor world but as we as Oracle
反应堆世界，但正如我们作为甲骨文一样
announced this week they've got work
宣布本周他们有工作
underway for a reactive JDBC driver so
反应性JDBC驱动程序正在进行中，因此
you know hopefully that pretends a
希望你假装
better a better situation in the coming
未来会有更好的情况
months three years for for JDBC access
JDBC访问需要三个月的时间
yep
是的
maybe final question because because
也许是最后一个问题，因为
we're right now out of time
我们现在没时间了
what what's what's your being comparing
你在比较什么
with Kafka so how that spring Rex is
和卡夫卡在一起，那春天的雷克斯怎么样
praying and compares with or intersects
祈祷并与之相交或相交
with Kafka this is these are neither
与卡夫卡，这是这些都不是
you know there Kafka is a message queue
你知道卡夫卡是一个消息队列
we have a project called spring for
我们有一个名为spring的项目
apache' Kafka and that is well supported
apache'Kafka，得到了很好的支持
at the spring front Patrick Kafka level
在春季前Patrick Kafka级别
as well as at as well as it's you know
以及在你所知道的
by the integration for spring
通过春季整合
integration so I'm gonna inbound and
整合，所以我要入站
outbound adapter for that and then we of
出站适配器，然后我们
course we have spring cloud streaming
当然我们有春季云流
binders for Patrick Kafka but
帕特里克·卡夫卡的粘合剂
Kafka is a myth is a message queue it's
卡夫卡是一个神话，它是一个消息队列
a message broker whereas the reactive
消息代理，而反应式
support that I demonstrated here is just
我在这里展示的支持只是
a way of composing pipelines inside of
一种在内部组成管道的方式
your single process you could guess that
您的单个过程中，您可能会猜到
pipeline to other nodes so the process
流向其他节点的流程
is by using register by using something
是通过使用某些东西来使用注册
like that but there's nothing
那样，但是什么都没有
necessarily that they don't necessarily
他们不一定
they don't necessarily connect or
他们不一定连接或
intersect got it so I think it's all the
相交得到了，所以我认为这就是全部
time we have for questions today and we
时间我们今天有问题，我们
should wrap up well thank George for
应该包好，谢谢乔治
your time
你的时间
yeah really appreciate it well thank you
是的，真的很感激，谢谢
very much for having me it was sooo much
对我来说非常非常
so much fun and again I want to
非常有趣，我想再次
encourage people to reach out at Josh
鼓励人们在乔希伸出援手
and Josh Lancome or at Starbucks
和Josh Lancome或星巴克
Manistee RBX a man should you have more
Manistee RBX一个男人，如果你有更多
questions comments or feedback thank you
问题评论或反馈谢谢
so much awesome thank you and thanks
太棒了，谢谢，谢谢
everyone for joining us have a good day
每个加入我们的人都过得愉快
and take care
还有，注意安全